Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station Records 1972.0001
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Correspondence, 1897-1920
  - Klunker, A. L., 1913-1915; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:182 (Box 6, Folder 182, Box-folder 6:182)
  - Knapp, C. M., 1910-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:183 (Box-folder 6:183, Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Knapp, E. E.-Knight, Bert, 1904-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:184 (Box 6, Folder 184, Box-folder 6:184)
  - Knight, Charles A., 1905-1913; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:185 (Box 6, Folder 185, Box-folder 6:185)
  - Knight, W. W.-Knowles, E. W., 1905-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:186 (Box 6, Folder 186, Box-folder 6:186)
  - Knowlton, Henry, 1908; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:187 (Box 6, Folder 187, Box-folder 6:187)
  - Knowlton, J. W., 1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:188 (Box-folder 6:188, Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Kny-Scheerer Company, 1906-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:189 (Box-folder 6:189, Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Koch, August, 1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:190 (Box-folder 6:190, Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Koch Brothers, 1902-1903; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:191 (Box-folder 6:191, Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Kochner-Komo, 1911-1912; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:192 (Box-folder 6:192, Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Koons, B. F., 1888-1897; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:193 (Box-folder 6:193, Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Kopelowf-Kyte, 1903-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:194 (Box-folder 6:194, Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Laboratory and School Supply Company, 1905-1906; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:195 (Box 6, Folder 195, Box-folder 6:195)
  - Labor-Lamb, Earl W., 1906-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:196 (Box-folder 6:196, Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Lamb Wire Fence Company, 1907; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:197 (Box-folder 6:197, Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Lamoronoeux-Lampard, 1902-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:198 (Box-folder 6:198, Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Lamson, G. H., 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:199 (Box-folder 6:199, Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Landers- Lane, C. B. (Miss), 1914-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:200 (Box-folder 6:200, Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Lane, C. B. (Mr.), 1895-1896; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:201 (Box-folder 6:201, Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Lane, Farnum-Lane, Sarah, 1904-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:202 (Box-folder 6:202, Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Lane. W. A., 1904-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:203 (Box 6, Folder 203, Box-folder 6:203)
  - Lang-Langmaid, 1904-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:204 (Box 6, Folder 204, Box-folder 6:204)
  - Langworthy, C. F., 1902; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:205 (Box-folder 6:205, Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Lanier-Lanton, 1904-1915; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:206 (Box 6, Folder 206, Box-folder 6:206)
  - Lapierre, Eugene, 1907-1908; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:207 (Box-folder 6:207, Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Larkham, H. J., 1911-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:208 (Box 6, Folder 208, Box-folder 6:208)
  - Larkin-Latham, 1910-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:209 (Box-folder 6:209, Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Lathrop-Laubscher, 1907-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:210 (Box 6, Folder 210, Box-folder 6:210)
  - Lauder, 1904-1907; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:211 (Box 6, Folder 211, Box-folder 6:211)
  - Lavanburg-Lawrence, 1907-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:212 (Box 6, Folder 212, Box-folder 6:212)
  - Lawson-Lazarus, 1904-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:213 (Box-folder 6:213, Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Leach-Leavans, 1904-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:214 (Box 6, Folder 214, Box-folder 6:214)
  - Leavens, George (Edmund Mortimer and Company), 1905; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:215 (Box-folder 6:215, Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Leavitt-Lee, Margaret, 1902-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:216 (Box 6, Folder 216, Box-folder 6:216)
  - Lee, Wilson H., 1903-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:217 (Box-folder 6:217, Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Leeds and Northrup-Leffingwell, Burton, 1905-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:218 (Box 6, Folder 218, Box-folder 6:218)
  - Leffingwell, C., 1909-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:219 (Box 6, Folder 219, Box-folder 6:219)
  - Leffingwell, Grove, 1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:220 (Box 6, Folder 220, Box-folder 6:220)
  - Legare, S. K., 1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:221 (Box-folder 6:221, Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Legg-Leincks, 1903-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:222 (Box 6, Folder 222, Box-folder 6:222)
  - Leith, Alfred, 1903-1909; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:223 (Box 6, Folder 223, Box-folder 6:223)
  - Lemieux-Leonard, 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:224 (Box 6, Folder 224, Box-folder 6:224)
  - Lersner-Levy, 1902-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:225 (Box-folder 6:225, Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Lewis, A. M.-Lewis, Harvey, 1905-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:226 (Box 6, Folder 226, Box-folder 6:226)
  - Lewis, H. Bertram, 1910-1915; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:227 (Box-folder 6:227, Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Lewis, H. R.-Lewis, Sarah, 1904-1916; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:228 (Box 6, Folder 228, Box-folder 6:228)
  - Leyden - Leys, 1911-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:229 (Box-folder 7:229)
  - Library Bureau, 1902-1905; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:230 (Box-folder 7:230)
  - Lieberam - Lipman, 1902-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:231 (Box-folder 7:231)
  - Lippincott - Longeway, 1902-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:232 (Box-folder 7:232)
  - Longley, R.I., 1917-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:233 (Box-folder 7:233)
  - Lonis-Louden, 1902-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:234 (Box-folder 7:234)
  - Louisiana, 1908-1912; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:235 (Box-folder 7:235)
  - Loue - Lowell Fertilizer, 1913-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:236 (Box-folder 7:236)
  - Lowell, Frank, 1910-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:237 (Box-folder 7:237)
  - Lowerre - Loyal, 1911 - 1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:238 (Box-folder 7:238)
  - Lucchini, V.E., 1904-1908; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:239 (Box-folder 7:239)
  - Luce, Daniel, 1913-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:240 (Box-folder 7:240)
  - Luddy, John, 1912-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:241 (Box-folder 7:241)
  - Ludlum - Lund, 1907-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:242 (Box-folder 7:242)
  - Lunt, Moss And Company, 1904-1905; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:243 (Box-folder 7:243)
  - Lurton, F.E., 1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:244 (Box-folder 7:244)
  - Lutters, Ernest, 1904-1905; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:245 (Box-folder 7:245)
  - Lux, Louis, 1908-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:246 (Box-folder 7:246)
  - Lyle - Lyman, A.B., 1909-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:247 (Box-folder 7:247)
  - Lyman, C.E., 1893-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:248 (Box-folder 7:248)
  - Lyman, Fred - Lynch, Edgar, 1915-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:249 (Box-folder 7:249)
  - Lynch, Wallace, 1908-1912; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:250 (Box-folder 7:250)
  - Lyon, S.H. - Lyon, W.H., 1909-1915; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:251 (Box-folder 7:251)
  - MacDaniel - Macdonald, 1910-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:252 (Box-folder 7:252)
  - Macey Co., 1905-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:253 (Box-folder 7:253)
  - MacGrath - MacMillan, 1907-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:254 (Box-folder 7:254)
  - MacMillan Co., 1910-1913; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:255 (Box-folder 7:255)
  - Macomber - Maindon, 1907-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:256 (Box-folder 7:256)
  - Maine, 1905-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:257 (Box-folder 7:257)
  - Makepeace - Manchester, Alison, 1907-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:258 (Box-folder 7:258)
  - A.W. Manchester, 1910-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:259 (Box-folder 7:259)
  - Manchester, E and Sons - Manchester, H.G., 1907-1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:260 (Box-folder 7:260)
  - Mandy Lee Incubator Co. - Mann, 1905-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:261 (Box-folder 7:261)
  - Manning, Charlotte, 1902; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:262 (Box-folder 7:262)
  - Mansfield, 1912-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:263 (Box-folder 7:263)
  - Manson Campbell Co. - Mara, 1908-1916; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:264 (Box-folder 7:264)
  - Marceau, 1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:265 (Box-folder 7:265)
  - March - Marden, Orth and Hastings, 1907-1912; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:266 (Box-folder 7:266)
  - Marion, G.L., 1907-1908; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:267 (Box-folder 7:267)
  - Markham, 1919-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:268 (Box-folder 7:268)
  - Markham, H.S., 1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:269 (Box-folder 7:269)
  - Marlin-Rockwell Co. - Marsh, 1908-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:270 (Box-folder 7:270)
  - Marshall, 1908-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:271 (Box-folder 7:271)
  - Martin & Allardyce - Martin, J.A., 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:272 (Box-folder 7:272)
  - Martin, W.S., 1910-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:273 (Box-folder 7:273)
  - Marvin - Marsland, 1911-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:274 (Box-folder 7:274)
  - Maryland, 1907-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:275 (Box-folder 7:275)
  - Masheck - Mason, William, 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:276 (Box-folder 7:276)
  - Mason, G.A., 1907; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:277 (Box-folder 7:277)
  - Massachusettes (1 of 3), 1903-1909; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:278 (Box-folder 7:278)
  - Massachusettes (2 of 3), 1909-1915; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:279 (Box-folder 7:279)
  - Massachusettes (3 of 3), 1916-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:280 (Box-folder 7:280)
  - Masse - Matenaers, 1910-1915; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:281 (Box-folder 7:281)
  - Matheson, Kenneth, 1910-1913; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:282 (Box-folder 7:282)
  - Mathewson - Mazzanovich, 1907-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:283 (Box-folder 7:283)
  - McAdam - McClave, 1907-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:284 (Box-folder 7:284)
  - McClave, S.W., 1912; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:285 (Box-folder 7:285)
  - McClean - McCord, 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:286 (Box-folder 7:286)
  - McCoy, 1910-1912; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:287 (Box-folder 7:287)
  - McCracken, 1918-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:288 (Box-folder 7:288)
  - McCreary - McCrorey, 1907-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:289 (Box-folder 7:289)
  - McDermott, 1907-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:290 (Box-folder 7:290)
  - McDonald - McDuffee, 1904-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:291 (Box-folder 7:291)
  - Mac Ewan - McIntosh, 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:292 (Box-folder 7:292)
  - McFarland, J.H., 1911-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:293 (Box-folder 7:293)
  - McGorty - McSherry, 1907-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:294 (Box-folder 7:294)
  - M.D. Knowlton - Meeker, 1907-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:295 (Box-folder 7:295)
  - Meekins, Packard & Wheat, 1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:296 (Box-folder 7:296)
  - Meharry - Merck & Co., 1902-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:297 (Box-folder 7:297)
  - Merrill - Messier, 1908-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:298 (Box-folder 7:298)
  - Metcalf, A.B., 1919-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:299 (Box-folder 7:299)
  - Metcalf, F.A. - Meygat, 1911-1915; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:300 (Box-folder 7:300)
  - Meyers, William S., 1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:301 (Box-folder 7:301)
  - Mianus Motor Works, 1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:302 (Box-folder 7:302)
  - Michigan, 1903-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:303 (Box-folder 7:303)
  - Mickle - Miles, 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:304 (Box-folder 7:304)
  - Miles, H.C.C., 1902-1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:305 (Box-folder 7:305)
  - Milhous, J.J. - Miller, A.O., 1911-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:306 (Box-folder 7:306)
  - Miller, Albert - Miller, W.H., 1902-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:307 (Box-folder 7:307)
  - Miller, W.W., 1903-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:308 (Box-folder 7:308)
  - Milliken, F.P. - Minor, M.W., 1902-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:309 (Box-folder 7:309)
  - Minnesota, 1903-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:310 (Box-folder 7:310)
  - Mississipi, 1903-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:311 (Box-folder 7:311)
  - Missouri, 1903-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:312 (Box-folder 7:312)
  - Mitchell - Mizutani, 1913-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:313 (Box-folder 7:313)
  - Moffatt - Molumphy, 1907-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:314 (Box-folder 7:314)
  - Monarch Paint Co., 1906; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:315 (Box-folder 7:315)
  - Monks, M.M. - Morehouse, F.S., 1914-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:316 (Box-folder 7:316)
  - Monroe Calculating - Monroe Hart & Sons, 1913-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:317 (Box-folder 7:317)
  - Montana, 1903-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:318 (Box-folder 7:318)
  - Monosom - Moon, 1905-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:319 (Box-folder 7:319)
  - Moore, C.J. - Moore, Rev. J., 1912-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:320 (Box-folder 7:320)
  - John C. Moore Corporation, 1912-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:321 (Box-folder 7:321)
  - Moore, R.A., 1911-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:322 (Box-folder 7:322)
  - Moore, M.H. - Moore, W.L., 1911-1916; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:323 (Box-folder 7:323)
  - Moreau Co. - Morrill press, 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:324 (Box-folder 7:324)
  - Morrill, A.B., 1911-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:325 (Box-folder 7:325)
  - Morris, F.L. - Morrison, H.C., 1902-1912; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:326 (Box-folder 7:326)
  - Morse, C. - Morse, W., 1906-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:327 (Box-folder 7:327)
  - Mortimer - Morton, 1908-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:328 (Box-folder 7:328)
  - Moseley, D.S., 1902; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:329 (Box-folder 7:329)
  - Moses, H.A. - Moses, S.M., 1913-1916; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:330 (Box-folder 7:330)
  - Moses, W.L., 1910-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:331 (Box-folder 7:331)
  - Mosler Safe Co., 1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:332 (Box-folder 7:332)
  - Moss, A.E., 1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:333 (Box-folder 7:333)
  - Moss, Charles E., 1908-1913; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:334 (Box-folder 7:334)
  - Motham, A.E. - Moyer, S.P., 1907-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:335 (Box-folder 7:335)
  - Mueller - Munroe, 1911-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:336 (Box-folder 7:336)
  - Munson, E.S. - Munson, W.H., 1911-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:337 (Box-folder 7:337)
  - Murch, H.A. - Murphy, W.E., 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:338 (Box-folder 7:338)
  - George Murphy Inc., 1908-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:339 (Box-folder 7:339)
  - Murray - Musser, 1908-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:340 (Box-folder 7:340)
  - Mycroft - Mynderse, 1911-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:341 (Box-folder 7:341)
  - F.E. Meyers & Bros., 1907-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:342 (Box-folder 7:342)
  - Meyers, W.S., 1902-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box7:343 (Box-folder 7:343)
- Correspondence (old box level inventory), 1882, 1888-1920, 1924, 1933-1947; 22.05 Linear Feet
  Agricultural Subjects in correspondence: pesticide use; San Jose Scale insects; metabolism experiments--carbon content; alcohol experimentation; fertilizers; cultivation of soy beans; Bordeaux Mixture (for fighting Blight); Chestnut Blight; leaf-miners; soil testing; alfalfa cultivation: sulfate of ammonia as pesticide; camembert cheese (Charles M. Jarvis); shropshire sheep; winter vetch; alfalfa hay; poultry testing; crop planting; pigs; white pine blister; model farms.
  - Correspondence, financial records, publications, legal documents, ephemera, 1889, 1894, 1896-1901, 1904-1914, 1917-1918, 1920, 1924; 1.3 Linear Feet Folders, Alphabetized C-D (Box 3)
    [Subjects include: Correspondence to and from: Professor W.L. Slate; Alfred Cochran; Thomas M. Cochrane; The Core Brass Manufacturing Company; The Coe Mortimer Company, Importers of Genuine Peruvian Guano, Manufacturers of E. Frank Coe's High Grade Fertilizers; Connecticut Board of Agriculture; Prof. L.A. Clinton; State Comptroller's Office (Thompson S. Grant, Comptroller; T.D. Bradstreet, Comptroller); "Corn" Magazine; Correspondence Insititute of America; Irving G. Davis; Corbin Screw Corporation.
    Publications: "Legislative Bulletin," Friday, March 3, 1899, and Tuesday, March 7, 1899; "An Act Concerning the State Board of Agriculture;" "Prospectus: Farmers' Institutes by the Connecticut State Board of Agriculture, in Cooperation with the State and Storres Experiment Stations for 1898-1899; Farmers' Convention Program (ephemera); "Handbook of Fairs and Dates: Issued by the State Board of Agriculture July 1, 1917."
    Agricultural subjects in correspondence: plant fertilization, pigeons, tobacco cultivation, bacteria for fertilization of crops, potato cultivation, manure application to crops, white leghorns, denatured alcohol, dairy bacteriology, decorative grasses, orchard cultivation, San Jose Scale insects.
    General Subjects: Storrs Agricultural School, Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station, University of Connecticut History.
  - Correspondence, postcards, posters, notes, financial records, legal documents, 1897-1898, 1903, 1906-1911, 1913-1918, 1920; 1.3 Linear Feet Folders, alphabetized E-G (Box 4)
    [Subjects include: Correspondence to and from: The E.C. Brown Company, Manufacturers of Pumps; E.D. Chittenden Company; E.D. Cummings; E.L. Freeman & Sons, Stationers, Printers, Binders; Meadow Brook Farm; Echo Farm, Litchfield, Connecticut; Electric Boat Company, Groton, CT; Edison Manufacturing Company; Eimer and Amend, Manufacturers and Importers of Chemicals and Chemical Apparatus; Du Pont; Federal Chemical Company; Federation of Jewish Farmers of America; Travelers Insurance Company; Maple Shade Farm; Pres. Charles Lewis Beach; Gardner Advertising Company, Essex, CT; James Gould Company.
    Agricultural and experimental subjects discussed in correspondence include: seed oats, seed potatoes, onion seed, suitable and unsuitable crops for cow pastures, weevils, Rhode Island Red eggs, potato beetles, Kjeldahl Flasks, thermometers, preparing soil with dynamite (for tree stump removal), barometers, ether, ground phosphate rock, alfalfa cultivation.
    Items regarding events: "New England Farm and Business Conference: Under the Auspices the Eastern States Agricultural and Industrial Exposition, Inc.: Held in Springfield, Mass., Sept. 15 and 16, 1916" (Poster); "Eastern States Exposition and Dairy Show, 1913."
    General Subjects: Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station, Storrs Agricultural School, University of Connecticut History.
  - Correspondence, postcards, notes, ephemera, 1896-1902, 1904, 1907-1913, 1915; 1.3 Linear Feet Folders, alphabetized G-H (Box 5)
    [Subjects include: Correspondence to and from: Grasselli Chemical Company; Prof. L.A. Clinton; Dr. Charles B. Graves, M.D.; F.W. Gray; C.D. Jarvis; W.O. Atwater; Great Britain Royal Agricultural Society; Yorkshire College; Cardiff Public Libraries; Board of Agriculture and Fisheries; Board of Agriculture for Scotland; J. Stillwell Grover; Hammond, Knowlton & Co., Silk Manufacturers; Pope Manufacturing Company, automobile manufacturer of Hartford, Conn.; Pres. R.W. Stimson; Holstein-Friesian Association of America; Russell Manufacturing Co.; L.D. Huff; D.Y. Hallock & Sons; Harder Manufacturing Company; Hoffmann, Ahlers & Co.; Hall Camera Co.; Pennsylvania Department of Agriculture; Hammond Typewriter Company; Pequot Poultry Farm; Melrose Castle Farm.
    Agricultural subjects in correspondence include: sulphuric acid, arsenate of lead (as insecticide), San Jose Scale insects, "Miscible oil for Spraying Purposes" (pesticide), treating peach trees and cherry trees against pests, Bordeaux Mixture (pesticide), production of Camembert Cheese, soluble oil (pesticide), poison content of carrots, peas and beans, Oyster Shell Scale (pest), milk-producing goats, dairy bacteria.
    Items related to Agricultural Events: "Horticultural Society of New York International Conference on Plant Hardiness and Acclimatization" schedule of events (ephemera).
  - Correspondence, manuscripts, photographs, legal documents, notes, 1893, 1895-1897, 1903-1904, 1908-1909, 1911-1912, 1915-1918, 1920; 1.3 Linear Feet Folders, alphabetized I-P (Box 6)
    [Subjects include: Correspondence to and from: University of Illinois; Iowa State University, Division of Veterinary Medicine (Ames, Iowa); Prof. L.A. Clinton; Second Congregational Church of Mansfield; Odd Fellows' Home of Connecticut; Central Vermont Railway Company; Prof. W.L. Slate; Hampden County (Mass.) Improvement League; State of Connecticut Board of Agriculture; Pres. Charles Lewis Beach; C.D. Jarvis; State Normal School of California; Leeds & Northrop Company; H.F. Judkins; Kentucky Tobacco Product Co.; Col. Charles Maples Jarvis; Herbert K. Job, State Ornithologist of Connecticut; R. Hart Geer; Horner's Zoological Arena: Wild Animal Importers; John B. Doolin, State Game and Fish Warden, Oklahoma; Chemical Laboratory, Wesleyan University; Benjamin Franklin Koons.
    Agricultural topics discussed in correspondence include: nitrate of soda, plant fertilizer, leaf blight, potato blight, creation of cheese, soluble oil (pesticide), arsenate of lead (pesticide), electrical measuring instruments, poultry manure, millet, fertilizing potatoes, quail disease.
    Publications and Manuscripts: Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station Bulletin no. 27, December, 1903 (fragment); "Problems in Fruit Growing" (Manuscript).
    General Subjects: Storrs Agricultural School, Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station, University of Connecticut History, Storrs, Connecticut History.
  - Correspondence, financial records, ephemera, publications, postcards, 1895-1896, 1902-1920; 1.3 Linear Feet Folders, alphabetized L-M (Box 7)